<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="93">
    <author>Nuggzy</author>
    <version>1.1.0.0</version>
<!--=================================================================-->
    <title>
        <en>Hemp Production System</en>
    </title>
    <iconFilename>hh_HempProdSystem.dds</iconFilename>
	<multiplayer supported="true"/>
	<fillTypes filename="xml/filltypes.xml" />	
<!--=================================================================-->	
    <storeItems>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/fast_grainFlourMill.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/farmerKioskSmall.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/hh_GreenHouse.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/hh_Factory.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/hh_TailorShop.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/hh_Bakery.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/pallet_hh_hemp.xml"/>		
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/pallet_hh_seeds.xml"/>		
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/pallet_hh_oil.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/pallet_hh_bread.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/pallet_hh_chocolate.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/pallet_hh_cookies.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/pallet_hh_cereal.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/pallet_hh_fabric.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/pallet_hh_paper.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/pallet_hh_clothes.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="xml/pallet_hh_brownies.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
<!--=================================================================-->
	<description>
        <en><![CDATA[Mod Name: Hemp Growing
Game: Farming Simulator 25

Description:
Enhance your Farming Simulator 25 experience with the Hemp Growing Mod, designed to add a new and exciting crop to your farm! This mod introduces a fully immersive hemp production system, including a Hemp Pallet, Grow House, and Selling Stand.

Features:
Hemp Pallet: A specialized pallet for transporting and storing hemp.
Grow House: A dedicated greenhouse structure designed to cultivate hemp plants efficiently.
Selling Stand: A unique selling point for hemp products.
]]>
		</en>
        <de><![CDATA[Mod-Name: Hanfanbau
Spiel: Landwirtschafts-Simulator 25

Beschreibung:
Verbessern Sie Ihr Landwirtschafts-Simulator 25-Erlebnis mit dem Hanfanbau-Mod, der entwickelt wurde, um Ihrer Farm eine neue und aufregende Nutzpflanze hinzuzufügen! Dieser Mod führt ein vollständig umfassendes Hanfproduktionssystem ein, einschließlich einer Hanfpalette, einem Grow House und einem Verkaufsstand.

Merkmale:
Hanfpalette: Eine Spezialpalette für den Transport und die Lagerung von Hanf.
Grow House: Eine spezielle Gewächshausstruktur für den effizienten Anbau von Hanfpflanzen.
Verkaufsstand: Ein Alleinstellungsmerkmal für Hanfprodukte.
]]>
		</de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Nom du module : Culture de chanvre
Jeu : Farming Simulator 25

Description:
Améliorez votre expérience Farming Simulator 25 avec le mod de culture du chanvre, conçu pour ajouter une nouvelle culture passionnante à votre ferme ! Ce mod introduit un système de production de chanvre entièrement immersif, comprenant une palette de chanvre, une maison de culture et un stand de vente.

Caractéristiques:
Palette de chanvre : Une palette spécialisée pour le transport et le stockage du chanvre.
Grow House : Une structure de serre dédiée conçue pour cultiver efficacement les plantes de chanvre.
Stand de vente : Un argument de vente unique pour les produits à base de chanvre.
]]>
        </fr>
	</description>
	
	<brands>
     <!-- <brand name="Allen" title="TBD" image="TBD.dds"/> -->
    </brands>

    <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/l10n"/>
</modDesc>

